Guide to the Sunset Magazine Records M2065
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Sunset Magazine records
1931-1998
1948-1969; 1977-1998
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Sunset Magazine (Firm)
M2065
172 Linear Feet (437 boxes, 2 map folders)
The records of Sunset Magazine primarily consist of over 100,000 photographs as published in the magazine from 1948-1969 and 1977-1998.
Scope and Contents
Following Sunset's move to Oakland from their iconic Willow West offices in Menlo Park in 2015, the magazine gave a great deal of material to Stanford University. The main part of the collection consists of the magazine's photo archive (frequently refered to as a periodical's "morgue") with prints, slides, transparencies and layouts from issues dating from 1948 to 1998, with an unfortunate gap from 1970 to 1976. There is also a small amount of administrative files, as well as sales presentation transcripts, advertising proofs, staff newsletters, a scrapbook, posters reproducing covers, and audiovisual media including a 1980 oral history with senior staff. Also present is a series of mounted photographs and depicting California Missions in the late 1930s and early 40s by Henry P. Schmidt from an exhibition sponsored by Sunset's Lane Publishing Company.
Sunset's photograph files contain approximately 100,000 photos. Prints are numbered "month-year-sequence" such as 1-85-001 for the first photo in the file for the January 1985 issue. The images were originally filed along with a notated issue indicating where the photos were printed as well as clippings from the magazine. Sunset published regional editions (South, North, and Central/Desert) mostly in order to tailor appropriate gardening advice; these are indicated in the listing. Some full issues starting in the late 1960s also include a "Guide for Cost of Contents." Following the last of the regular issue files, there are a few folders of prints from related publications Quick, Light, & Healthy (1997), Western Campsites (1972-1980) and Western Travel Adventures (1978-1980). The photographers most frequently credited on prints include Ged T. Fitzgerald, Robert Cox, Moulin Studios, Jon Brenneis, Ernest Braun, Dennis Galloway, Laing Photos, Russell Illig, Blair Stapp, Tom Burns, and Glenn Christiansen.
While the collection does contain published issues along with selected prints used in them, no effort has been made to describe the images themselves here. Given Sunset's focus as the "Magazine of Western Living," however, one may expect to find photographs of gardening and landscaping, architecture and home improvement, cooking and food, entertaining, travel, nature, and recreation. In order to use the collection, patrons should refer to indices to the magazine.
An index from 1997-2009 is available from Sunset here: http://www.sunset.com/sunset-magazine-annual-index.
As part of a 1998 centennial project, Stanford hosts a bibliography of select articles here: http://web.stanford.edu/dept/SUL/library/sunset-magazine/html.
Physical copies of indices from 1952-2009 printed by Sunset have been cataloged: https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/11813180.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use. Audiovisual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Sunset Magazine, 2015.
Related Materials
Stanford holds several collections related to Sunset, including the following:
Laurence W. "Bill" Lane, Jr. papers, circa 1953-2010 (M1811) https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/9153981
Sunset Magazine: video, 18 Oct. 1998 (MISC 596) Produced by Channel 7 as "Sunday on Seven: Bay Area Trends; People, Places, Events" and hosted by Rose Guilbault. Includes interviews of Mel and Bill Lane. https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/4084868
A Century of Western Living, 1898-1998: centennial keepsakes, 1998 (MISC 548) Exhibit catalog, copy of the original May 1898 issue, pin, and ephemera. https://searchworks.stanford.edu/view/4084799
Stanford also has catalogued most of the many books published by Sunset.
West (U.S.) -- Pictorial works; West (U.S) -- Periodicals; Sunset Magazine (Firm); Sunset Magazine (Firm)
- Photograph files
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-01 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - January 1948 magazine (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - 1-48-006 to 1-48-139, 1948-01 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-02 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - February 1948 magazine (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - 2-48-007 to 2-48-170, 1948-02 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-03 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - March 1948 magazine (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - 3-48-000 to 3-48-031, 1948-03 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - 3-48-34 to 3-48-131, 1948-03 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - 3-48-159 to 3-48-201, 1948-03 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-04 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - April 1948 magazine (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - 4-48-002 to 4-48-240, 1948-04 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - 4-48-002 to 4-48-240, 1948-04 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-05 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - May 1948 magazine (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - 5-48-002 to 5-48-261, 1948-05 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - 5-48-002 to 5-48-261, 1948-05 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-06 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - June 1948 magazine (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 6-48-003 to 6-48-194, 1948-06 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-07 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - July 1948 magazine (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - 7-48-002 to 7-48-112, 1948-07 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - 7-48-160 to 7-48-198, 1948-07 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-08 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - August 1948 magazine (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - 8-48-003 to 8-48-126, 1948-08 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-09 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - September 1948 magazine (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - 9-48-003 to 9-48-112, 1948-09 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - 9-48-114 to 9-48-199, 1948-09 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-10 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - October 1948 magazine (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - 1-48-001 to 10-48-192, 1948-10 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-11 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - November 1948 magazine (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - 11-48-002 to 11-48-104, 1948-11 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - 11-48-105 to 11-48-269, 1948-11 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1948-12 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - December 1948 magazine (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 12-48-003 to 12-48-058, 1948-12 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - 12-48-060 to 12-48-155, 1948-12 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-01 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - January 1949 magazine (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - 1-49-001 to 1-49-096, 1949-01 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-02 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - February 1949 magazine (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - 2-49-001 to 2-49-110, 1949-02 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - 2-49-112 to 2-49-186, 1949-02 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-03 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - March 1949 magazine (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - 3-49-001 to 3-49-170, 1949-03 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-04 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - April 1949 magazine (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - 4-49-001 to 4-49-201, 1949-04 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-05 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - May 1949 magazine (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - 5-49-003 to 5-49-122, 1949-05 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-06 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - June 1949 magazine (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - 6-49-001 to 6-49-134, 1949-06 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-07 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - July 1949 magazine (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - 7-49-000 to 7-49-169, 1949-07 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-08 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - August 1949 magazine (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - 8-49-001 to 8-49-172, 1949-08 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-09 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - September 1949 magazine (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 9-49-001 to 9-49-226, 1949-09 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-10 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - October 1949 magazine (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - 10-49-001 to 10-49-098, 1949-10 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - 10-49-113 to 10-49-201, 1949-10 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-11 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - November 1949 magazine (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - 11-49-002 to 11-49-175, 1949-11 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1949-12 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - December 1949 magazine (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - 12-49-001 to 12-49-077, 1949-12 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - 12-49-078 to 12-49-210, 1949-12 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-01 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - January 1950 magazine (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - 1-50-004 to 1-50-186, 1950-01 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-02 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - February 1950 magazine (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 2-50-002 to 2-50-200, 1950-02 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-03 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - March 1950 magazine (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 3-50-001 to 3-50-140, 1950-03 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 3-50-151 to 3-50-201, 1950-03 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-04 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - April 1950 magazine (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 4-50-014 to 4-50-208, 1950-04 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - 4-50-210 to 4-50-315, 1950-04 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-05 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - May 1950 magazine (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - 5-50-001 to 5-50-256, 1950-05 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-06 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - June 1950 magazine (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - 6-50-015 to 6-50-220, 1950-06 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-07 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - July 1950 magazine (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - 7-50-003 to 7-50-160, 1950-07 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-08 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - August 1950 magazine (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - 8-50-002 to 8-50-190, 1950-08 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-09 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - September 1950 magazine (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 9-50-002 to 9-50-130, 1950-09 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - 9-50-133 to 9-50-262, 1950-09 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-10 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - October 1950 magazine (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - 10-50-000 to 10-50-215, 1950-10 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-11 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - November 1950 magazine (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 11-50-001 to 11-50-197, 1950-11 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1950-12 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - December 1950 magazine (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - 12-50-000 to 12-50-131, 1950-12 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-01 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - January 1951 magazine (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - 1-51-000 to 1-51-141, 1951-01 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-02 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - 2-51-002 to 2-51-091, 1951-02 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - February 1951 magazine (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - 2-51-093 to 2-51-228, 1951-02 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-03 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - March 1951 magazine (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - 3-51-001 to 3-51-247, 1951-03 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-04 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - April 1951 magazine (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - 4-51-002 to 4-51-173, 1951-04 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - 4-51-174 to 4-51-311, 1951-04 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-05 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - May 1951 magazine (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - 5-51-001 to 5-51-131, 1951-05 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - 5-51-131 to 5-51-224, 1951-05 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-06 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - June 1951 magazine (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - 6-51-000 to 6-51-197, 1951-06 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-07 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - July 1951 magazine (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 7-51-001 to 7-51-151, 1951-07 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-08 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - August 1951 magazine (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - 8-51-000 to 8-51-217, 1951-08 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-09 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - September 1951 magazine (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - 9-51-000 to 9-51-075, 1951-09 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - 9-51-076 to 9-51-202, 1951-09 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-10 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - October 1951 magazine (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - 10-51-000 to 10-51-105, 1951-10 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - 10-51-106 to 10-51-205, 1951-10 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-11 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - November 1951 magazine (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - 11-51-000 to 11-51-148, 1951-11 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1951-12 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - December 1951 magazine (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - 12-51-002 to 12-51-186, 1951-12 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-01 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - January 1952 magazine (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 1-52-000 to 1-52-187, 1952-01 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-02 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - February 1952 magazine (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 2-52-000 to 2-52-090, 1952-02 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 2-52-091 to 2-52-241, 1952-02 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-03 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - March 1952 magazine (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 3-52-000 to 3-52-138, 1952-03 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 3-52-141 to 352-231, 1952-03 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-04 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - April 1952 magazine (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 4-52-000 to 4-52-095, 1952-04 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 4-52-096 to 4-52-206, 1952-04 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 4-52-207 to 4-52-362, 1952-04 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-05 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - May 1952 magazine (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - 5-52-001 to 5-52-131, 1952-05 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - 5-52-132 to 5-52-272, 1952-05 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-06 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - June 1952 magazine (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - 6-52-001 to 6-52-071, 1952-06 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - 6-52-072 to 6-52-150, 1952-06 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - 6-52-151 to 6-52-266, 1952-06 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-07 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - July 1952 magazine (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - 7-52-001 to 7-52-202, 1952-07 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-08 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - August 1952 magazine (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - 8-52-001 to 8-52-059, 1952-08 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 8-52-060 to 8-52-250, 1952-08 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-09 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - September 1952 magazine (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - 9-52-000 to 9-52-125, 1952-09 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - 9-52-126 to 9-52-294, 1952-09 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-10 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - October 1952 magazine (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - 10-52-001 to 10-52-117, 1952-10 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - 10-52-119 to 10-52-287, 1952-10 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-11 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - November 1952 magazine (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - 11-52-001 to 11-52-105, 1952-11 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - 11-52-106 to 11-52-270, 1952-11 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1952-12 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - December 1952 magazine (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - 12-52-000 to 12-52-090, 1952-12 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - 12-52-095 to 12-52-202, 1952-12 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-01 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - January 1953 magazine (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - 1-53-000 to 1-53-078, 1953-01 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - 1-53-081 to 1-53-155, 1953-01 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-02 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - February 1953 magazine (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - 2-53-002 to 2-53-93, 1953-02 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - 2-53-095 to 2-53-197, 1953-02 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-03 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - March 1953 magazine (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - 3-53-000 to 3-53-125, 1953-03 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - 3-53-126 to 3-53-297, 1953-03 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-04 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - April 1953 magazine (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - 4-53-003 to 4-53-112, 1953-04 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 4-53-114 to 4-53-226, 1953-04 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - 4-53-232 to 4-53-354, 1953-04 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-05 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - May 1953 magazine (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - 5-53-001 to 5-53-074, 1953-05 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - 5-53-075 to 5-53-190, 1953-05 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - 5-53-191 to 5-53-307, 1953-05 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-06 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - June 1953 magazine (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - 6-53-000 to 6-53-105, 1953-06 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - 6-53-106 to 6-53-209, 1953-06 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - 6-53-210 to 6-53-322, 1953-06 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-07 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - July 1953 magazine (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - 7-53-000 to 7-53-076, 1953-07 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - 7-53-077 to 7-53-201, 1953-07 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-08 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - August 1953 magazine (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - 8-53-000 to 8-53-060, 1953-08 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - 8-53-061 to 8-53-180, 1953-08 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-09 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - September 1953 magazine (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - 9-53-000 to 9-53-124, 1953-09 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - 9-53-126 to 9-53-193, 1953-09 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - 9-53-194 to 9-53-302, 1953-09 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-10 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - October 1953 magazine (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - 10-53-000 to 10-53-111, 1953-10 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - 10-53-114 to 10-53-205, 1953-10 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - 10-53-207 to 10-53-287, 1953-10 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - 10-53-288 to 10-53-400, 1953-10 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-11 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - November 1953 magazine (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 11-53-000 to 11-53-101, 1953-11 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - 11-53-103 to 11-53-205, 1953-11 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - 11-53-206 to 11-53-298, 1953-11 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 11-53-310 to 11-53-435, 1953-11 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1953-12 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - December 1953 magazine (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - 12-53-000 to 12-53-096, 1953-12 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 12-53-102 to 12-53-264, 1953-12 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-01 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - January 1954 magazine (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - 1-54-000 to 1-54-159, 1954-01 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-02 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - February 1954 magazine (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - 2-54-000 to 2-54-090, 1954-02 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - 2-54-091 to 2-54-232, 1954-02 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-03 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - March 1954 magazine (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - 3-54-000 o 3-54-207, 1954-03 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - 3-54-208 to 3-54-294, 1954-03 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - 3-54-297 to 3-54-409, 1954-03 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-04 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - April 1954 magazine (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - 4-54-000 to 4-54-164, 1954-04 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - 4-54-165 to 4-54-244, 1954-04 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - 4-54-245 to 4-54-372, 1954-04 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-05 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - May 1954 magazine (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - 5-54-000 to 5-54-105, 1954-05 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - 5-54-108 to 5-54-232, 1954-05 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - 5-54-235 to 5-54-390, 1954-05 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-06 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - June 1954 magazine (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - 6-54-000 to 6-54-095, 1954-06 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - 6-54-096 to 6-54-234, 1954-06 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - 6-54-235 to 6-54-330, 1954-06 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-07 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - July 1954 magazine (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - 7-54-000 to 7-54-082, 1954-07 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - 7-54-083 to 7-54-151, 1954-07 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 7-54-162 to 7-54-253, 1954-07 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-08 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - August 1954 magazine (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - 8-54-000 to 8-54-089, 1954-08 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - 8-54-090 to 8-54-146, 1954-08 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - 8-54-147 to 8-54-267, 1954-08 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-09 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - September 1954 magazine (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - 9-54-001 to 9-54-097, 1954-09 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - 9-54-098 to 9-54-193, 1954-09 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - 9-54-202 to 9-54-330, 1954-09 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-10 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - October 1954 magazine (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - 10-54-000 to 10-54-081, 1954-10 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - 10-54-082 to 10-54-129, 1954-10 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - 10-54-221 to 10-54-247, 1954-10 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - 10-54-248 to 10-54-295, 1954-10 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - 10-54-300 to 10-54-313 and 10-54-137 to 10-54-195, 1954-10 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-11 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - November 1954 magazine (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - 11-54-000 to 11-54-088, 1954-11 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - 11-54-090 to 11-54-172, 1954-11 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - 11-54-173 to 11-54-288, 1954-11 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1954-12 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - December 1954 magazine (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - 12-54-003 to 12-54-150, 1954-12 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - 12-54-151 to 12-54-269, 1954-12 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-01 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - January 1955 magazine (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - 1-55-000 to 1-55-110, 1955-01 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - 1-55-111 to 1-55-193, 1955-01 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-02 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - February 1955 magazine (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - 2-55-001 to 2-55-115, 1955-02 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - 2-55-120 to 2-55-172, 1955-02 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - 2-55-172 to 2-55-257, 1955-02 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-03 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - March 1955 magazine (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - 3-55-001 to 3-55-088, 1955-03 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - 3-55-089 to 3-55-164, 1955-03 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - 3-55-165 to 3-55-238, 1955-03 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - 3-55-239 to 3-55-361, 1955-03 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-04 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - April 1955 magazine (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 4-55-000 to 4-55-105, 1955-04 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - 4-55-106 to 4-55-204, 1955-04 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - 4-55-205 to 4-55-276, 1955-04 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - 4-55-277 to 4-55-386, 1955-04 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-05 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - May 1955 magazine (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 5-55-000 to 5-55-111, 1955-05 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - 5-55-112 to 5-55-197, 1955-05 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - 5-55-198 to 5-55-264, 1955-05 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 5-55-265 to 5-55-350, 1955-05 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 5-55-351 to 5-55-451, 1955-05 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-06 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - June 1955 magazine (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - 6-55-000 to 6-55-102, 1955-06 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - 6-55-104 to 6-55-191, 1955-06 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 6-55-192 to 6-55-245, 1955-06 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - 6-55-246 to 6-55-332, 1955-06 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-07 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - July 1955 magazine (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - 7-55-000 to 7-55-053, 1955-07 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - 7-55-054 to 7-55-131, 1955-07 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - 7-55-132 to 7-55-251, 1955-07 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-08 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - August 1955 magazine (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 8-55-000 to 8-55-074, 1955-08 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - 8-55-075 to 8-55-156, 1955-08 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - 8-55-157 to 8-55-266, 1955-08 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, South and North, 1955-09 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - September 1955 magazine (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - 9-55-000 to 9-55-077, 1955-09 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - 9-55-078 to 9-55-161, 1955-09 (Box 60, Folder 4)